i still
haven't had
any offers
to buy my mansion
come on guys seriously
do i have to do this
for sale one diamond
please buy
really
i can't even sell this building and this
prime piece of real estate for one
diamond
oh man
this is really bad and also i was here
just checking up on this because no one
i thought maybe someone might have like
left me a sign but no but i turned over
here
ah
there's a little swedish meatball
looking at me
from a gigantic tombstone and i thought
i'll check this out
rip
iscap let's take a look dear hermits
i have now stayed alive for a total of
170 hours which i have not afk'd at all
i seem completely immortal i am now
auctioning away my demise to the highest
bidding oh my goodness iskall still
playing demise
seems like a long time ago to
participate get a bid box rename it to
your name place a bid in diamonds and
the auction is silent so if you do not
win the auction you get your
diamondbacks uh you may kill me in any
way you seem fit
once okay maybe not multiple times may
the richest hermit win
i'm not the richest hermit
but i have got a couple of diamonds
let's let's maximize this i don't know
how many people it's a silent auction so
we have no idea how how other people are
gonna do this
so
i've got nothing to lose really why not
let's do it all of my diamonds
off you go all of them 50 stacks
forget it
oh it's gone there's no there's no take
backsies
oh
okay uh
do i regret that
yeah i kind of regret that maybe i
should have thought this through for a
second is iskall's death really worth it
okay well if i win
if somehow this goes through and i win
um i'm definitely going to have to make
the most spectacular
death frisco possible um all right well
let's go let's crack on shall we we are
heading back to my base where we are
going to do something
well a little bit sad actually now you
may remember what my base looks like and
for those of you that don't remember
it is basically a giant towel if it
would load
it's basically a giant
[Laughter]
sorry i forgot about my shulker box
monster
it is a giant tower some sort of
futuristic thing i don't know it's a bit
odd but it was shaped this way for a
very specific reason
and more importantly this bit here being
able to go all the way down
through flying but this wasn't made just
for flying through myself this is
actually going to be
how i leave this planet how i leave this
minecraft world because
i am here to announce that
this is actually the second to last
episode of my hermitcraft season on
season six i feel like the time here has
come so my next episode will
unfortunately be the last one of season
six and then whenever season seven
happens we'll be back with some new
antics new stories and everything else
so
what we're going to do is prepare to
leave season 6 for our next episode and
i thought what better way to do that
than to launch ourselves through this
base
and into space
so in order to make a rocket we're going
to need a
do a little bit of preparation first of
all we need to clear out that space up
there and then we need to make a launch
pad and indeed the rocket itself which
means a little bit of slime block
trickery
that i'm not actually very good at the
last thing we want is our rocket
catching and snagging on one of these
man i haven't been up here in such a
long time there's a bunch of parrots and
stuff here okay so that takes care of
that now if we go down here we can set
up the launch area so we need like a
silo we need to find the center of this
we probably have a few things to sort of
set up before we uh we leave season six
but
i want to go out in style so we might as
well do this
as best as we can so next episode will
be the finale of this season but it's
going to be a bit of a special episode
so make sure you don't miss it because
it will be important for the next season
okay we've got to make a rocket that's
going to fit in this tiny tiny space oh
no oh no no no no no no not the portrait
cave no
okay that's as deep as it goes
so this is where the floor has to be no
matter what
because there's a um there's a a
mysterious cave down there belonging to
someone nothing to do with me so i'm
gonna match what's up there
to this uh
i'm gonna match the shape of this
exactly to here so i know how big my
rocket has to be this is a very small
rocket i must admit this is going to be
a bit of a tight squeeze all right it's
going to be a bit of a dinky rocket but
it will be fine it'll be fine now we've
got to fill this out to get rid of all
the water and we can start construction
on this thing now i have a slight
confession to make
i have never really truly understood
slime block machines never i just i just
can't seem to wrap my head around it i
almost need mumbo to give me like
i need i need some tutoring and oh no
i kept some redstone boxes but i've left
a redstone box upstairs
oh no it's in the monster
let's see if we can find it this will
either take two seconds or half an hour
hello
hello chester that's that was the name
that everyone said in the comments and i
love it so this is chester
um i need a redstone shulker box please
be kind okay it's probably in a red box
like this but that's not it uh the worst
case scenario is it's right in here
where i can't get to it
ah
yes yes yes yes it's yes it's too oh
it's right on the outside thank you
chester thank you
oh man i was getting a little bit scared
that i'd never i'd never find it okay
thank you chester right so
i
will be the first one to admit
that i don't really know
how to do actually wait a minute
mumbo has made a flying machine
over there there we go
look at that he made his flying chair
this is basically what i need not sure
how it works exactly
we need to study this
we've got an observer
yep i really know i don't really know
what this is doing
but this is this is pretty slender this
will this will make its way out of the
top a-okay so
let's do a little time lapse of me
absolutely failing to get this made and
we'll we'll just do our best we'll just
do our best
okay so
i think everyone knows kind of what i'm
going to go for i'm recreating what we
just saw with mumbo jumbo's rocket and
i'm just going to add as many blocks as
possible but i actually messed up during
this and i wanted to kind of highlight
it so i essentially recreated everything
with the slime blocks block for block
but then i just placed something upside
down just for a second and i thought oh
i need to get rid of this block and of
course that then sent everything in the
wrong direction and ruined it of course
because it then connected to the floor
so i had to redo it and i'm so glad i
didn't go for a bigger rocket because i
was gonna mess it up at some point and
have to redo it several times i think
this is actually quite poetic because
this sums up my redstone skills and
i think this is the best way to leave
season six through the base that i spent
ages making
this is uh this is not the best rocket
this is not this is this is not the
definition of leaving season six in
style
but this is the only thing that i'm like
100 sure is actually gonna work and on
top of that it's one of the only things
that's actually going to fit inside
the base it's not a particularly wide
gap so
what we're gonna do is we're gonna put
the minecart on here get rid of this
thing and i hope uh how am i gonna
activate this
i feel like i haven't thought things
through
so
we're gonna have to have some sort of
redstone signal
going down there that's gonna activate
things
i would like to summon all of you for a
little meeting announcing the demise in
scout or isco auction oh yeah i i
totally forgot about my beard can we
meet in the shopping district
so what i'm thinking whoa
that was weird
anyway i'll put that there because what
i can do
is i'll stand on here oh wait no i still
can't see it
right so if i put it here what i can do
is send a signal using this button
all the way down
it could it would basically just power
that piston there that extends it
detects with his little observer face
and then off we go into space
i'm full of the rhymes today
so in theory i hop in here
does that work
no
that no that doesn't work
i thought maybe i have to use a bow and
arrow let's try again
no
we're gonna have to rethink this anyway
it looks like i need to go meet up with
those guys anyway i was going to do this
where i
throw that it activates and up we go
that's how we're going to activate this
thing to get out of here but let's go
and meet up with iscal and
impulse and stress
impulse and green a
yeah
is this a is this all the bidders
this is all a bit this is i mean not a
lot of people have been playing on this
song lately okay but i'm i'm happy that
there's only three what i'm not happy
about is
the amounts
i i'm just i'm just a little bit curious
um you can see that i'm clearly safe in
this little box at the moment but yes
[Laughter]
[Applause]
well your head's kind of big yeah you
got a big head
okay i i know that one of you
has earned the right to kill me but
let's not get ahead of ourselves
let's not get ahead of ourselves i have
made
a little thing
for you all to stand on and i'm gonna
announce the winner okay oh is it this
is it what i'm standing on right now i
was gonna say get off that's my spot up
there i i thought green was already
declaring himself the winner yeah
well be surprised
i just want to say i
i thought that i would make maybe 10
diamonds from this but you all bid it
it's 10 diamonds isn't gonna cut it
sorry um no one bid 10 diamonds though
are you guys ready to hear the result
yes
yes yes did i can i kill you
in the third place
and to be stood on the dire bird poo
plate of doom
i'm sorry stressed by 24 diamond blocks
they don't make it
you get them back though stress
yeah yeah i'm not gonna you know i'm not
gonna grumble about that because i am
pretty skinned
but come on i am like mining for that
and everything i put like the uh
but at least i've gone back now i
suppose but i kind of oh yeah okay wait
till you hear the winning amount all
right okay yes
because the winner
and the person only buy a few diamond
blocks that has the right to kill me
is impossible
actually the box is empty yeah
the box is empty
i put in every diamond i had everything
64 box of diamonds and green bits oh my
god that is ridiculous how are you doing
so much well i can tell you how i
afforded that one i i bet on iskall to
win demise and i want a ton of diamonds
by doing that so
and i didn't really think about it i'm
hoping that you'll have fun with this
one i'm also oh yeah terribly terribly
scared
going to be yeah no actually actually
actually i'm not completely out i am
giving you impulse sv
one week you got one week to complete
your idea for killing me one week
wow one week okay that is exciting yeah
i can get i can get something
impulse it better be yeah yeah yeah
now i'm feeling the pressure i cannot
wait
it's gonna be trust me
that's a shame but at least we got
60 diamonds 60 and a half diamonds back
that's pretty that's pretty good going
um but i'm a bit gutted i really thought
i really thought i can't believe it i
can't believe that this
wasn't enough
diamonds honestly
that's so many but impulse is actually
still online maybe i could ask him if he
wants to like half it because what i
could do he put in 64 diamond blocks so
what i could do
is i could say
i'll give you 32 diamond blocks and then
we can go halvesies on it actually yeah
i'm going to do that i'm going to do
that
impulse you got a sec at my base
yep bert
[Music]
[Laughter]
congratulations on winning iskall's
death i guess thank you thank you
appreciate that you were super close i
was really surprised i couldn't have won
if i tried but i actually had some some
ideas for his death and i wondered if he
wanted maybe if i gave you half the
amount that you paid i.e 32 diamond
blocks
maybe you want to share the death you
know you kill half of this no i'll kill
the other half of this scale yeah we'll
just split them right in half we'll go
oh
yeah you know what i i like that i do
have some ideas myself and if you have
ideas and we combine those ideas i'm
thinking this could potentially be
awesome i think we make it like the most
elaborate death we're not just it's not
about it's not about his actual death
it's not about the bit in chat that says
a scout has died it's about the journey
to his death in my opinion and i think
maybe between us we can come up with the
most and we've got a week as well it
could be the best thing that we oh yeah
i agree i agree so yes i accept your
proposal uh i do appreciate splitting
the uh getting the 32 diamond blocks
back for the deal too so i got some
money back as well this is worked out we
both we both get the same experience but
for half the price excellent all right
man so yeah let's put our heads together
and let's come up with the most
elaborate epic death for iskall ever
so after having a little conversation
with impulse off camera we've got a
let's just look at the background look
at the can you see it can you see
[Laughter]
after having a little discussion with
impulse
what we've discussed
we think we want to keep it a secret
because
i know you guys now it's it's been many
episodes of shenanigans and i can't
trust you to keep secret anymore so i
don't want iska to know what adventure
he's going on okay so i'm not gonna tell
you our plans but impulse and i have
discussed it and we are going to send
iskow on
probably the craziest adventure i will
tell you this though he doesn't have to
move a muscle he won't have to do
anything he'll just be said sit here and
then let the journey begin but i'm not
gonna reveal any of our plans but i tell
you what it is probably going to take us
a week to make because my goodness
so we've got quite a lot to look forward
to in the final episode of season six
but before we depart there's actually
one thing i need to do
i need to head back to the shopping
district
because
unbelievably nobody
wants my haunted mansion
here we are for sale one diamond please
i've given up you know what this is so
ridiculous now
for sale
for -10 diamonds
take
the
house
there we go look
just for i will give you money i will
give you 10 diamonds to take this thing
somebody
please i know it's i know i'm not going
to be i would like to sell this before i
leave season six anyway that is the end
of today's episode and remember please
please please turn up for the finale of
season six because hopefully we can do
quite a lot of things not to mention we
are going to rip
iscow impulse and i are going to create
something quite magnificent and i've got
a whole bunch of other things that i
want to do in the finale of this season
so thank you very much for watching as
always and i'll see you
in the next and last episode good bye